kraken.io 2019-05-04

# Privacy Policy · Kraken.io

### General Information

Please read these Terms carefully, and contact us if you have any questions. By using Kraken, you agree to be bound by these Terms and our Privacy Policy.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web pages and the quality of our service, and is not shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial purposes.

### Information Gathering and Usage

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or fill out a form.

We use collected information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, and research.

We keep your information only so long as we need it to provide Kraken to you and fulfil the purposes described in this policy.

At any time you may decide to stop using our services and ask us to remove all the information we collected when you first registered on our site. To do that, please contact us here: [support@kraken.io](mailto:support@kraken.io)

### Data Protection

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, financials, etc.) will NOT be stored on our servers. Once you enter your credit card information it will be encrypted and send to our Payment gateway providers’ database.

### Cookies Policy

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive.

Cookies are required to use the Kraken service.

We use cookies to record current session information, but do not use permanent cookies. You are required to re-login to your Kraken account after a certain period of time has elapsed to protect you against others accidentally accessing your account contents.

### Disclosure

We may disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas or when your actions violate the Terms of Service.

### Third Party Links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This Privacy Policy was last modified on: **May 18, 2018**
